export const questionsJson = [{
     question: "What is 8 x 1",
     answers: [5,6,7,8],
     correctAnswer: 8
   },{
     question: "What is 1 x 1",
     answers: [1,2,3,4],
     correctAnswer: 1
   },{
     question: "What is 2 x 2",
     answers: [1,2,3,4],
     correctAnswer: 4
   }
   ,{
     question: "What is 10 x 2",
     answers: [20,5,4,1],
     correctAnswer: 20
   },{
     question: "What is 95658 / 6",
     answers: [15941,15942,15943,15944],
     correctAnswer: 15943
   },{
     question: "What is 1 / 0",
     answers: ["WTF",1,0,"inf"],
     correctAnswer: "inf"
   },{
     question: "What is 1 + 1 * 2",
     answers: [3,4,2,"none of above"],
     correctAnswer: 3
   },{
     question: "What is (0 * 2 + 2 * 3) * (2 - 2)",
     answers: [0,6,4,1],
     correctAnswer: 0
   },{
     question: "What is 1 - 1",
     answers: [2,0,5,6],
     correctAnswer: 0
   },{
     question: "What is 1 + 1 + 2 + 3 + 4",
     answers: [10,11,12,9],
     correctAnswer: 11
   }];



/* export const questions=[
  {
   id: 1,
   description: 'What is 5 x 9',
   choice: [
     '45', '30', '25', '20'
   ],
   answer: 0
 },
 {
   id: 2,
   description: 'Most common vehicle on the road',
   choice: [
     'Airplane', 'Helicopter', 'Car', 'Boat'
   ],
   answer: 2
 },
 {
   id: 3,
   description: 'Rides on two wheels',
   choice: [
     'Car', 'Motorcycle', 'Airplane', 'Boat'
   ],
   answer: 1
 },
 {
   id: 4,
   description: 'Georgia (USA) is famous for these',
   choice: [
     'Apple', 'Grape', 'Lemon', 'Peach'
   ],
   answer: 3
 },
 {
   id: 5,
   description: 'Grown in Hawaii',
   choice: [
     'Peach', 'Pineapple', 'Lemon', 'Grape'
   ],
   answer: 1
 }
]

*/
